<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Competitive Programming Club</title>
    <description>A student club at the University of Adelaide.</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 20:01:47 +1030</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 20:01:47 +1030</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICPC Regionals 2020</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, 63 teams of young programmers competed in the International Collegiate Programming Contest across the South Pacific region. 14 out of these 63 teams were from our club, making it the most active competitive programming community in all of South Pacific region!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Huge congratulations to&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BotezGambit (Ragav Sachdeva, Brandon Smart, Rijul Ramkumar) for placing 9th in Division 1.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nameless (Hamish Spencer, Billy Roberts, Kosta Tsekouras) for placing 8th in Division 2.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +1030</pubDate>
        <link>/ICPC-Regionals-2020/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/ICPC-Regionals-2020/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2021 Committee Elections</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone, following our AGM last night we have officially locked in a new commitee for 2021!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to the new team and looking forward to see the great things you will do for the club!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting from the right of the image here is the new team-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;President- Ralf Saroar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vice President- Rijul Ramkumar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Events Coordinator- Sarah Damin&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Industry Liason- Matthew Michael&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Secretary- Vikhyat Sharma&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Treasurer- Shyla Lee&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Web Developer- Joph Larena&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +1030</pubDate>
        <link>/2021-committee/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2021-committee/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICPC Divisionals 2018</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ICPC divisional finals has officially ended! This year we had 4 teams from UofA, all of which put in great effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The first position was bagged by Stinkypete (Yuanjing Zhao, Hoang Vinh Dinh, Christo Pyromallis) - they solved 11/12 problems and got themselves an overall rank of 6 i.e. they are going to regionals for sure (although official notices have yet to come)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The second position was bagged by TensorMellow (Miguel Martin, Farbod Motlagh, Ragav Sachdeva) - they solved 10/12 problems and got themselves an overall rank of 14 (it’s likely they won’t make it to regionals due to their high time penalty though).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The third position was bagged by 3SpacesPerTab (Brandon Smart, Chris Shi) - they solved 8/12 problems and got themselves an overall rank of 26. Note: that it was a team of 2 only and both being FIRST year students.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are great results and we look forward to the results of regionals!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +1030</pubDate>
        <link>/ICPC-Divisionals-2018/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/ICPC-Divisionals-2018/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
